[Music]
i'm so excited to announce the launch of
my new bc strength 45 hyper now we've
been working on this for two years it
took a lot of time to get it just right
and now it's perfect so first i'm going
to show off the features then i'm going
to show you how we use it at glute lab
all beginners start out with body weight
we have two different methods the first
is the neutral neutral feet straight
spine in neutral this works a good blend
of hamstring glutes and erectors and the
second method is the glute dominant
method that's round back feet flares so
this is going to turn her feet out at 45
degree angle round her back tuck her
chin and she's just gonna push her hips
into the pad she does not unravel the
spine and this is more gluten hammy
takes the erectors out of it now a final
body weight variation we do is 45 hyper
pulses and you put your arms in front of
you like this and you just do the top
half of the movement squeezing the
glutes really hard
this is amazing we do three sets of 20
to 30 reps now a staple at glute lab is
the dumbbell variation all right
alyssa's going to grab the dumbbell
holds it in front of her and she just
does
full range repetitions
usually we do neutral neutral but you
can also do feet flared and rounded
either one works we have girls doing 100
pound 45 degree hypers for 20 plus reps
band 45 degree hypers have actually
surpassed dumbbells in popularity we do
more of these than anything
so
uh we just wrap the bands over the upper
back and then alyssa starts pumping out
the reps you can do these
rounded or neutral either one works
we typically do three sets of 20 reps
with these and then a final variation we
do a lot at glute lab is the prisoner
single leg so this is going to take one
leg out all right she puts her hands
behind her neck and these are full range
reps she's going to go deep
and come all the way back up this
annihilates the hammies we typically do
three sets of 12 reps with these all
right so i've probably used a hundred
different 45 degree hyper units during
my lifetime and this is my absolute
favorite i'm not just saying that
because it's bc strength it truly is my
favorite
now the first thing i want to point out
is that this thing ships affordably we
made it in multiple pieces so they can
come apart and be less expensive to ship
that's always a challenge with these
products you know most commercial gym
pieces are very expensive to ship well
this thing has a commercial gym feel to
it without the commercial gym shipping
cost so this is a feature i used with my
hip thruster
most people put band pegs out this way
so it stretches your bands awkwardly and
increases the wear and tear on them by
putting the t setting there you can put
the bands and it's a much more natural
stretch for the bands the handles need
to be out wide enough so they don't
interfere while you're performing 45
degree hypers especially for bigger men
like me now we put a handle here to make
it for easy adjustments okay
now the lowest setting
this fits someone who's four foot eleven
five foot tall now the highest setting
hole 10
this fits someone who's six foot eight
so i'm pretty sure the bc strength 45
hyper offers the largest height range
out of all the products on the market i
mean check this out i'm six foot four
and this is at my belly button right
here so this will accommodate a very
tall person now these thigh pads are
angled in and i really love this feature
it makes for a much more comfortable
much smoother feeling while you're
performing the movement now there's also
a gap in the middle here which is
convenient for men for obvious reasons
now there's nice high quality grip tape
on here so your feet don't slip now
there was one flaw associated with
making the unit compact and affordable
with shipping and that was that the unit
would tip a little bit so to solve that
problem we just put plate pegs on there
and for the occasional person like me
who's super tall and really strong at
these this prevents any rocking of the
unit whatsoever now it's a beautiful
unit you're gonna love having this in
your garage it conveys high quality the
colors are magnificent the way the light
blue pops and most important this thing
is sturdy it's built to last you can use
up to 500 pounds of resistance with
combined body weight and external
resistance so if you're a 200 pound man
you could be doing 300 pound barbell 45
degree hypers if you wanted and this
thing will last so the 45 rehyper it's a
staple movement in all of my programs i
endeavored to make the best 45 degree
hyper on the market and i believe i've
done it pick yours up today
you